Jason Mabry

\: 276.632.2490

1: 276.734.2747

I am a dedicated IT professional with nearly a decade of experience in the field. I have extensive experience in server configuration, maintenance, and backup, including Windows, Linux, and Mac OS X Server. I am a lifelong learner who enjoys a challenge and thrives on making things easier for the end user. I love learning about new technologies that can help the users I support in their day-to-day lives.



Skills	Servers/Infrastructure/Cloud	Development	Other
	 Active Directory Administration Group Policy, File & Print Services, RADIUS/LDAP, AVG Google Apps Administration Office 365 Administration VMWare Meraki Networking and MDM Cisco Routing and Switching Mac OS X Server Linux Server Administration 	 HTML5/CSS Ruby on Rails PHP GitHub WordPress 	 3D design and printing Troubleshooting Problem Solving Works well individually or with a team

Experience

Piedmont Governor's School

IT Specialist — 2012-present

- Responsible for the maintenance of all technology including, laptops, desktops, Kindles, iPads, printers, etc.
- Responsible for the maintenance of and updates to school website.
- Designed and developed an online application system for prospective students of the Governor's School.
- Set up and maintain Google Apps for Education domain services.
- Oversee all aspects (design, printing, maintenance, etc) of Makerbot Replicator 23D printing system.

New College Institute

IT Specialist — 2012-present

- Responsible for the administration and maintenance of an Active Directory Domain including ADDS, DNS, DHCP, DFS, WSUS, and Antivirus
- Responsible for a complex network, consisting of Cisco and Meraki wireless and wired

technologies.

- Instrumental in upgrading our domain from Windows 2003 functional level to Windows 2008.
- Integral in the migration of several aging physical servers to a virtualized environment using VMware ESXi servers.
- Maintain and troubleshoot Polycom Video Tele-conferencing system and complex AV room setups controlled by Extron/Crestron controllers.
- Implemented Nagios monitoring service that monitors network devices and notifies IT staff if there is a problem.
- Responsible for the migration, configuration, and maintenance of Microsoft's Office 365 for Education.
- Configured and implemented an off-site backup/disaster recovery plan using Amazon's S3/Glacier services to store weekly VM server backups.
- Highly involved with the IT and infrastructure planning of a 50,000 square foot educational facility that opened in 2014.
- Member of several committees, including Technology, Marketing, and Security/Safety.

Henry County Public Schools

 $Computer\ Technician - 2006-2012$

- Responsible for the upkeep and maintenance of all technology in two middle school buildings where technology is a major part of education.
- Administrator of large Active Directory Domain, including designing and implementing Group Policies for managing domain computers and users.
- Implemented network-based computer imaging system to streamline configuration.
- Implemented network monitoring system that sends email and SMS notifications when network equipment is down or malfunctioning.
- Instrumental in planning and implementing a mass deployment of Apple iPads to students, faculty, and administrators.
- Administrator of Google Apps for Education domain services.
- Responsible for customization and administration of Student Information System servers and web application.

Education

Radford University

Major: Computer Science

Concentration: Software Engineering

Patrick Henry Community College

Major: Information Systems Technology

Concentration: Programming

References

Available on request